Toybox 0.8.12-android multicall binary (see https://landley.net/toybox)

usage: toybox [--long | --help | --version | [COMMAND] [ARGUMENTS...]]

With no arguments, "toybox" shows available COMMAND names. Add --long
to include suggested install path for each command, see
https://landley.net/toybox/faq.html#install for details.

First argument is name of a COMMAND to run, followed by any ARGUMENTS
to that command. Most toybox commands also understand:

--help		Show command help (only)
--version	Show toybox version (only)

The filename "-" means stdin/stdout, and "--" stops argument parsing.

Numerical arguments accept a single letter suffix for
kilo, mega, giga, tera, peta, and exabytes, plus an additional
"d" to indicate decimal 1000's instead of 1024.

Durations can be decimal fractions and accept minute ("m"), hour ("h"),
or day ("d") suffixes (so 0.1m = 6s).
